[
    {
        "question": "What was Australia's former name?",
        "optionA": "Bosnia",
        "optionB": "New Amsterdam",
        "optionC": "New Holland",
        "optionD": "Andorra",
        "answer": "New Holland"
    },

    {
        "question": "Cabbage contains what percentage of water?",
        "optionA": "32 percent",
        "optionB": "10 percent",
        "optionC": "2 percent",
        "optionD": "91 percent",
        "answer": "91 percent"
    },

    {
        "question": "What was the first name for the hashtag symbol (#)?",
        "optionA": "Pound sign",
        "optionB": "Number sign",
        "optionC": "Zed mark",
        "optionD": "Octothorp",
        "answer": "Octothorp"
    },

    {
        "question": "What is the best selling musical instrument in the world?",
        "optionA": "Harmonica",
        "optionB": "Accordion",
        "optionC": "Guitar",
        "optionD": "Drums",
        "answer": "Harmonica"
    },

    {
        "question": "Who lived at 221B, Baker Street, London?",
        "optionA": "Tony Stark",
        "optionB": "Morgan Freeman",
        "optionC": "Sherlock Holmes",
        "optionD": "Samuel L. Jackson",
        "answer": "Sherlock Holmes"
    },

    {
        "question": "Which of these animals does not sleep?",
        "optionA": "Lion",
        "optionB": "Bullfrog",
        "optionC": "Owl",
        "optionD": "Zebra",
        "answer": "Bullfrog"
    },

    {
        "question": "All members of which musical group could not read or write music?",
        "optionA": "AC/DC",
        "optionB": "The Rolling Stones",
        "optionC": "Metallica",
        "optionD": "The Beatles",
        "answer": "The Beatles"
    },

    {
        "question": "Which human body part contains the most water?",
        "optionA": "Eye",
        "optionB": "Lung",
        "optionC": "Tongue",
        "optionD": "Liver",
        "answer": "Lung"
    },

    {
        "question": "Which fruit contains more sugar than a strawberry?",
        "optionA": "Lemon",
        "optionB": "Avocado",
        "optionC": "Olive",
        "optionD": "Lime",
        "answer": "Lemon"
    },

    {
        "question": "Which natural food never spoils?",
        "optionA": "Apple",
        "optionB": "Honey",
        "optionC": "Cotton Candy",
        "optionD": "Ginger",
        "answer": "Honey"
    }
]